2022/O FIFA/ORGANIZATION soccer/O Haiti/PERSON Aristide/PERSON return/O Mexico/LOCATION drug/O war/O NIST/ORGANIZATION computer/O security/O Pakistan/LOCATION diplomat/O arrest/O murder/O phone/O hacking/O British/MISC politicians/O Toyota/MISC Recall/MISC Egyptian/MISC protesters/O attack/O museum/O Assange/MISC Nobel/MISC peace/O nomination/O Oprah/PERSON Winfrey/PERSON halfsister/O release/O of/O The/O Rite/PERSON Thorpe/PERSON return/O in/O 2012/O Olympics/MISC White/MISC Stripes/MISC breakup/O William/PERSON and/O Kate/PERSON fax/O savethedate/O Cuomo/PERSON budget/O cuts/O Taco/ORGANIZATION Bell/ORGANIZATION filling/O lawsuit/O healthcare/O law/O unconstitutional/O Amtrak/ORGANIZATION train/O service/O Super/LOCATION Bowl/LOCATION seats/O TSA/ORGANIZATION airport/O screening/O reduce/O energy/O consumption/O Detroit/ORGANIZATION Auto/ORGANIZATION Show/ORGANIZATION global/O warming/O and/O weather/O Keith/PERSON Olbermann/PERSON new/O job/O State/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION the/ORGANIZATION Union/ORGANIZATION and/O jobs/O Dog/PERSON Whisperer/PERSON Cesar/PERSON Millans/PERSON techniques/O MSNBC/O Rachel/PERSON Maddow/PERSON Sargent/PERSON Shriver/PERSON tributes/O Giffords/PERSON recovery/O protests/O in/O Jordan/LOCATION Egyptian/MISC curfew/O Beck/PERSON attacks/O Piven/PERSON Holland/O Iran/LOCATION envoy/O recall/O Kucinich/PERSON olive/O pit/O lawsuit/O White/LOCATION House/LOCATION spokesman/O replaced/O political/O campaigns/O and/O social/O media/O organic/O farming/O requirements/O Egyptian/MISC evacuation/O carbon/O monoxide/O law/O 
