BBC/ORGANIZATION World/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION staff/O cuts/O NSA/ORGANIZATION Kubica/ORGANIZATION crash/O release/O of/O Known/O and/O Unknown/LOCATION Emanuel/LOCATION residency/O court/O rulings/O US/LOCATION unemployment/O Special/O Olympics/MISC athletes/O Moscow/LOCATION airport/O bombing/O Obama/PERSON birth/O certificate/O Bottega/LOCATION Veneta/LOCATION 
